Let's scroll down here and update this headings text.
دعونا نقوم بالتمرير لأسفل وتحديث نصوص هذه العناوين.
Now, to make it a bit easier to read.
الآن، لتسهيل قراءة النص قليلًا.
I'm just going to bump up the font size a bit.
سأقوم بتكبير حجم الخط قليلًا.
Now that I've selected the element in the DOM,
وبما أنني قد قمت بتحديد العنصر في DOM،
let's use the "$0" trick to store this element in a variable.
فلنقم باستخدام خاصية "$0" من أجل تخزين هذا العنصر في متغير.
Now that I've stored this element in a variable,
وبما أنني قمت بتخزين العنصر في متغير،
which we can see here,
وهو ما نراه هنا،
let's update the text of this element.
فلنقم بتحديث نص هذا العنصر.
Using the "textContent" property and setting it to this string,
باستخدام خاصية "textContent" وتعيينها في تلك السلسلة.
we can see that even though we're adding HTML right here.
يمكننا أن نرى أنه بالرغم من أننا أضفنا HTML هنا.
That HTML is still being displayed over here in the actual rendered page.
يستمر عرض ملف HTML في تلك الصفحة المعروضة بالفعل.
Now, let's compare the "textContent" property
والآن، دعونا نقارن خاصية "textContent".
with setting the same string with the "innerHTML" property.
بإعداد نفس السلسلة باستخدام خاصية "innerHTML".
So, using the same string with the HTML characters,
لذلك، فإن استخدام نفس السلسلة بحروف HTML،
this now shows up as rendered HTML because we're using the "innerHTML" property.
يظهر هذا على هيئة ملف HTML نظرًا لاستخدامنا خاصية "innerHTML".
So "textContent" displays everything as text
إذًا تعرض خاصية "textContent" كل شيء على هيئة نص
while "innerHTML" will render any HTML in the string.
بينما سيعرض "innerHTML" أي ملف HTML في السلسلة.